Hey guys, long day, huh? Listen, I appreciate it —
thanks for moving on all this without me.
Happy to.
Quick turnaround, I understand. I didn't know something as complex
as production capacity could become available so quickly.
Exciting, right?
Yes, exciting. Don't worry about it.
It's like a dance, but to faster music. Like…
Double time.
Dance. I like that. Okay, we have 45 minutes
before we meet with Apoorva. Let's dance.
Catch me up on where you're at and, you know, your thinking.
Do I? You go ahead.
So the main question is: does ClickBrush stand a chance
in the toothbrush market, right?
So Manish and I thought of everything that influences
a customer's decision to purchase. Like colour…
Size, grip, packaging — everything we need to know.
We thought it through.
Okay.
It's not cheap: 50 lakh rupees to get all the information we need. But it's going
to give us a really clear view into whether customers will buy the product.
It's high.
Hey, better safe than sorry, right?
I mean, I'm sure Apoorva would agree.
All right. Thanks for putting so much thought into this.
The price tag…
It's steep.
Yes, Arun, but if we just—
It's a third of the budget.
For this one decision.
Okay.
Let's think this through.